functionloops.com 2018-07-22

# Privacy Policy

_Effective date: **May 21, 2018**_

 **Function Loops Privacy Policy**

Function Loops LTD is a sound design company based in Israel.

This page informs you about how we collect, use, and disclose your personal data when you use our website ( _https://www.functionloops.com_ ) and the choices you have associated with that data.

You will also find information about how you can affect the processing of your personal data, as well as what rights you have as user of this website.

We use your data to provide and improve the website. By using the website and all the services associated with it, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

 **What Data Do We Collect?**

Function Loops LTD collects several types of data with the main purpose of providing and improving the website, user experience and service.

Here is what data we may collect:

Customers:

  * email address
  * first name and last name
  * transaction ID
  * purchase date
  * paid amount
  * payment method (if PayPal or card was used in the purchase, but no card details are kept)
  * IP address (necessary for fraud protection)

Newsletter:

  * e-mail address
  * name
  * marketing consent

We collect your email address and your name after you make a purchase, during promotions (sale campaigns, giveaways, contests etc) and though sign-up forms on the site.

We may also collect information about how our website is accessed and used. This usage data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our website and hold certain information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to properly use some portions of our website.

 _INFO: Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze the service._

 **Why We Collect Your Data?**

Here is a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data:

  * to register you as a new and/or as a prospective customer;
  * to deliver your purchase(s);
  * to contact you with email newsletters, offers or other marketing materials;
  * to send you additional information about our products and services;
  * to manage our relationship with you which may include notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy, to ask you leave a review or take a survey;
  * to provide support;
  * to follow up after correspondence;
  * to provide and maintain our services and improve user experience.

 **How Long We Store The Data?**

Function Loops LTD will retain your information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this policy. Function Loops LTD will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your information to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We also retain log files (usage data) for internal analysis purposes. These log files are generally retained for a short period of time, except where they are used for website security or to improve the functionality of our service, or we are legally obligated to retain them for longer time periods.

 **Who Receives Your Data?**

We use third parties to supply digital products and services to you on our behalf, including payment processing, delivery of goods, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The third parties may require access to some or all of your data. We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

The third parties we are currently working with are Payloadz, Google Analytics, Facebook Business and Mailchimp.

  * if you make a purchase you will be redirected to a third party service called **Payloadz** , you can read their privacy policy here: <https://www.payloadz.com/privacy.asp>;
  * we use **Google Analytics** , a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. Visit Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>;
  * we use **Facebook Business** for marketing purposes, read their privacy policy here: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>;
  * we use **Mailchimp** to periodically send newsletters and promotion campaigns, read their privacy policy here: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>.

We use embedded content on our store. Links to some of the privacy policies of the most common services have been included below:

  * Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update ](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update%20%20%20)
  * SoundCloud: <https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy>
  * YouTube (Google): <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

 **Do We Store Or Collect Payment Card Details?**

We do not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The third-party payment processors we currently use are  **Payloadz**  and **Paypal** , read their privacy policy here: <https://www.payloadz.com/privacy.asp> and <https://www.paypal.com/il/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.

 **​Do We Transfer Your Data To Third Countries?**

Yes. Your data may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Israel and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including personal data, to Israel and process it there.

 **Is Your Data Secure With Us?**

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **Links To Other Websites**

On our website you may find links to other websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of every website you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party websites or services.

 **What Are You Rights Regarding How We Process Your Data?**

You have the right to:

  * obtain access to your personal data we process, also request correction;
  *  request erasure or restriction of your personal data;
  * request transfer of your personal data;
  * withdraw a given consent at any given time;
  * submit complaints regarding our processing of your personal data.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, you are welcome to contact us by using the contact details set out here: <https://www.functionloops.com/contact.html>.

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may refuse to comply with your request if is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Our website and services does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your children has provided us with personal data, please contact us: <https://www.functionloops.com/contact.html>.

 **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this privacy policy.

You are advised to review this privacy policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

 **Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, don't hesitate to contact us: <https://www.functionloops.com/contact.html>.
